Preview of the next issue
Aruida FightiN'Driving
Noyonara
Dream faucet and black out
A my line
I want to come true with you
Tears
Good morning
Good bye.
We are about to fly to Aichi prefecture to participate in a re-release and festival.
This time, I'd like to try this ame-chare project.
What?
It's called: Greaser Jiao De Battle!
Bite. I bit in.
It's morning, I can't talk.
What time is it?
It's 7:30.
Sorry. Minus points for the morning.
Are you awake?
I'm up.
I'm up every time.
That's normal.
Plus 5 points.
Yes! It's sweet.
Zero, five, zero, minus.
Throughout the day, you'll be challenged to various quizzes and games.
And the winner will get a ride in the green car, me, a successful celebrity!
You mean only one of you?
Yes, that's right.
No way!
So it will be a lonely scene with three people on a normal bullet train and only one person in the green car.
It's lonely, but you can sleep on the way home.
It's great to sleep comfortably in a spacious place.
That's for sure.
And it's a sign of success.
I'm happy just to say that I rode in the Green Car.
I take a lot of pictures in the green car.
That's for sure.
Let's all do our best to make it a little better, and keep our spirits up.
Well, I'm off to Aichi!
I'm off!
Actually, I got a shield book!
I can choose from all kinds of clothes and ribbons and stuff.
Sounds like a lot of fun!
I'm going to enjoy it!
On the flight time
I can hear the plane now.
I'm fine in the morning
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to check it out.
Checking in.
I'm checking now.
I'm fine in the morning
I want to sleep again
Here we are!
Here it comes!
Oh, no!
I'll drop it as soon as I can
The moment I arrived...
Stop it!
I'm scared.
Yes, sir.
Too soon?
Quickly?
What is it? A problem.
Question, please.
What is the role of Jal?
What's Jal's part?
Oh no, let's not!
That's disgusting.
I never thought about it.
It could work, right?
It'll work.
It's a quick push.
Are you sure?
I might cross.
Hey.
Gentle Agent Roomba.
I wonder what's the one thing that's still blurry?
Japan Entrance Land.
Yes, sir.
One for each of you, so it's push-pull.
The one who pushes the fastest wins.
It's Hana-san, isn't it?
Japan Airlines.
What?
There it is.
I overdid it with the blurbs.
Let's do one more.
Okay.
One more question.
The manager, Mr. Morimichi, touched it.
The number I was touching, for me, was
Fifty-three.
Ah.
53 H53 H.
Eh?
54 H.
Ooh.
That's great.
54 H.
I didn't even remember what number I was touching.
There it is, there it is.
So this is what I'm talking about.
I'll have to make sure I get it right.
That's right.
Mr. Tomitsumi was asleep the moment he sat down.
He was sleepy.
But for Ayanan, she was awake and didn't understand.
No, you don't.
Well then...
I'm off to Tokonami.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll be back later.
Thank you.
Matsumoto, are you okay with the mountains?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
I think I'll be fine. Thank you.
You know, if you don't give up, you won't waver.
Not one step at all.
Uh Uh Uh Uh
Escape from here
I want to get out of this one tatami
The same moment with you
My feelings for you
Because it's not time like this anymore
I can't talk about it
You're like a cupic
My feelings for you
What's the best message you can give me?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Don't stop I'm a flow you're mine
You're like a mythrip
hahaha
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Please, please, please
No I don't play games
I wanna be your magnet
I'm a flow you're mine
Don't stop I'm a flow you're mine
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
Take the climax
Please you don't miss it
Watch the back of summer
I'm here!
I don't have time
I don't have time for this.
What's your full name, BPM Maeda?
Oh, wait.
I always say it.
Wait, not now.
Wait a minute.
She calls me Mae-chan.
No, no, no. You call me downstairs.
Say it so I can hear.
Maeda, Mayu-chan
Manalo, Manalo
Miyu.
Mayuko
Mychka
What should I do, Mychka?
Hinch, hinch
It starts with na
Natsumi
Maeda, Natsuki
Natsuko
Natsume!
We're screwed!
Are you sure you can make it to the mountains in summer?
Yes, I'm fine.
Watch Natsume's back.
I love you, Myra.
I love you.
You're the best. Thank you very much.
I'm off.
Oh!
I'm off!
I love you.
No, I love you.